<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PETRI NETS 2022</title>
    <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on PETRI NETS 2022</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Petri Nets 2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://petrinets2022.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/home/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Petri Nets 2022 The 43rd International Conference on Application and Theory of Petri Nets and Concurrency with affiliated workshops, advanced tutorials, and the Petri nets PhD course will take place in Bergen, Norway on 19 June - 24 June, 2022.
News  For the welcome reception on tuesday (today) it is very important to be on time as the doors to Håkonshallen will be closed at 20.00. The M NORD entrance of the building (the one closer to the tram stop) is locked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accepted Papers</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/accepted/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/accepted/</guid>
      <description> To be announced
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programme</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/programme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/programme/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Established in 2004 by the International Institute for Software Technology of the United Nations University (UNU-IIST, currently known as the United Nations University Institute in Macau), the ICTAC conference series aims at bringing together researchers and practitioners from academia, industry and government to present research and exchange ideas and experience addressing challenges in both theoretical aspects of computing and the exploitation of theory through methods and tools for system development. ICTAC also aims to promote research cooperation between developing and industrial countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RV Lectures @ ICTAC</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/rvlec/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/rvlec/</guid>
      <description>RV Lectures @ ICTAC, Nov. 30 / Dec. 1 Supported by the Norwegian Research Council FORSTERK-project COEMS Training Network.
Volker Stolz, Jose Ignacio Requeno, Martin Leucker Runtime Verification of Streams with TeSSLa Sandro Stucki, Gerardo Schneider, Cesar Sanchez Gray-box Monitorability of Hyperproperties &amp;ndash; the Case of Data Minimization Ezio Bartocci et al. Monitoring Cyber-Physical Systems Dejan Ničković Runtime verification for rigorous engineering of cyber-physical systems Giles Reger Monitoring with Data  Practicalities  Venue: Online (Zoom) Time: tbd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Bergen</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/bergen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/bergen/</guid>
      <description>The city of Bergen Bergen is a world heritage city and the gateway to the Fjords of Norway. The city is well-connected to all major European flight hubs.
  More information on VisitBergen
Bergen Weather Heard bad things about Bergen weather? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, we&amp;rsquo;ve ordered reasonable weather! Check the forecast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accommodation</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/accommodation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/accommodation/</guid>
      <description>Bergen is full of centrally located hotels, which are 5-6 tram stops (around 10 mins) away from the conference venue (tram stop: Kronstad). Here we list some hotels in various price ranges in decreasing order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ATAED workshop</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/ataed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/ataed/</guid>
      <description>Programme - Tuesday, June 21 Room: M004
9:00 – 10:30 Session 1: Welcome and invited talk  Sander Leemans, Full Professor RWTH Aachen University. Leveraging frequencies in event data: a pledge for stochastic process mining  10:30 – 11:00 Coffee Break (Room: M130/131)
11:00 – 12:30 Session 2: Stochastics &amp;amp; Statistics  Jarne Vandenabeele, Gilles Vermaut, Jari Peeperkorn and Jochen De Weerdt. Enhancing Stochastic Petri Net-based Remaining Time Prediction using k-Nearest Neighbors [PDF] Patrizia Schalk and Lisa Petrak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carl Adam Petri Speaker</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/paulo-verissimo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/paulo-verissimo/</guid>
      <description>Prof. Paulo Esteves-Verissimo (King Abdullah University of Science and Technology, Saudi Arabia)  Assumptions in computer science: mere mathematical hypotheses, or representations of the physical world? [Abstract in PDF]
The praxis of algorithm or mechanism design, especially in concurrent or distributed systems, mandates clear statements of the assumptions underlying the design, such as topology, dimension, synchrony, performance, threats, etc. The design &amp;mdash; say, of an algorithm whose behaviour is defined by a set of properties (safety, liveness) &amp;mdash; is then shown correct by demonstrating it does secure those properties, given the assumptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference Venue</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/venue/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/venue/</guid>
      <description>The conference will take place in the K2 building at Campus Bergen of Western Norway University of Applied Science. You can easily reach the building from either Bergen city centre or Bergen airport by tram (light-rail)
The conference venue / Campus is just next to the stop &amp;ldquo;Kronstad&amp;rdquo;.
  
Western Norway University of Applied Sciences Western Norway University of Applied Sciences is one of the largest higher education institution in Norway with approximately 1,800 employees and 16,000 students distributed on five campuses in Førde, Sogndal, Bergen, Stord and Haugesund.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HEDA workshop</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/heda/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/heda/</guid>
      <description>Programme Monday 20 June 2022 Project meeting (by invitation only)
 Tuesday 21 June 2022 09:00 - 10:45 Session 1: Opening, Keynote and Short Presentations  Keynote: Health Sense Markus Bertl, Gunnar Piho and Peeter Ross. Exploratory Analysis of Health Insurance Billing Data from People with Psychiatric Diseases in Estonia: An Opportunity for Data Science and Artificial Intelligence? Jaroslaw Pasiak, Wojciech Pasiak, Harald Soleim, Remy Andre Monsen, Atle Birger Geitung, Guri-Elise Holgersen and Thomas Fiskeseth Larsen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invited Speaker</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/diekert/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/diekert/</guid>
      <description>Prof. Volker Diekert (University of Stuttgart, Germany)  Petri Nets and Mazurkiewicz Traces Partnership when Honeymoon is Forgotten [Abstract in PDF]
History. In the mid 1970-ties it became clear that free partially commutative monoids play a central role for the analysis and the understanding of concurrent systems. The foundations were developed in the 1973 JACM-paper by Robert Keller [1]. A few years later, in 1977 Antoni Mazurkiewicz published his seminal Aarhus technical report where he showed that, indeed, partial commutation describes the semantics of one-safe Petri nets perfectly [2].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invited Speaker</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/huisman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/huisman/</guid>
      <description>Prof. Marieke Huisman (University of Twente, the Netherlands)  VerCors and Alpinist: correctness of GPU applications throughout the development cycle GPU programs are widely used in industry. They make use of special hardware, supporting massive parallelism. To avoid the introduction of errors, we can augment GPU programs with (pre- and postcondition-style) annotations to capture functional properties. The VerCors program verifier, a verifier for concurrent software, has been tailored to reason about such GPU programs, and in this talk I will explain how this is done, and discuss various GPU case studies that have been verified with VerCors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keynote Speakers</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/keynotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/keynotes/</guid>
      <description>Carl Adam Petri Speaker  Prof. Paulo Esteves-Verissimo (King Abdullah University of Science and Technology, Saudi Arabia) Assumptions in computer science: mere mathematical hypotheses, or representations of the physical world? (Read more &amp;hellip;)

 Invited Speakers  Prof. Volker Diekert (University of Stuttgart, Germany) Petri Nets and Mazurkiewicz Traces Partnership when Honeymoon is Forgotten (Read more &amp;hellip;)

 Prof. Marieke Huisman (University of Twente, the Netherlands) VerCors and Alpinist: correctness of GPU applications throughout the development cycle (Read more &amp;hellip;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local Weather</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/weather/</guid>
      <description> Daily weather forecast for Bergen
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Main Track</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/mainconference/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/mainconference/</guid>
      <description>Schedule for the main conference track The main conference track will take place in Room M003.
Wednesday, 22 Jun | Thursday, 23 Jun | Friday, 24 Jun
Wednesday 22 June 2022 9:00 – 9:30 Welcome and openning session 9:30 – 10:30 Distinguish Carl Adam Petri Lecture (Chair: Maciej Koutny)  Paulo Esteves-Verissimo: Assumptions in computer science: mere mathematical hypotheses, or representations of the physical world?  10:30 – 11:00 Coffee Break (Room: M130/131)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Model checking contest</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/mcc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/mcc/</guid>
      <description>Programme for the model checking contest The model checking contest will take place on Tuesday afternoon 16.00 - 17.30 in room M003.
For further information, see https://mcc.lip6.fr/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petri Net Course</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/pncourse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/pncourse/</guid>
      <description>Sunday, 19 Jun | Monday, 20 Jun | Tuesday, 21 Jun
The Petri Net Course takes place from Sunday 19 to Tuesday 21.
This course offers a thorough introduction to Petri Nets in four half-day modules on Sunday and Monday with an option of a tutorial module (tuesday) on applications of Petri Nets and/or new developments presented by experts in the area. Each module of the course can be taken separately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PNSE workshop</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/pnse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/pnse/</guid>
      <description>Programme Room: M004
9:00 – 10:30 Session 1: Welcome and keynote (H. Rölke)  Einar Broch Johnsen (University of Oslo): Digital Twins - An Emerging Paradigm for Model-Centric Engineering  10:30 – 11:00 Coffee Break (Room: M130/131)
11:00 – 12:30 Session 2: Long paper presentations (25+5)  Federica Adobbati, Luca Bernardinello, Görkem Kılınç Soylu and Lucia Pomello: Information flow among transitions of bounded free-choice nets Bart-Jan Hilbrands, Debjyoti Bera and Benny Akesson: Partial Specifications of Component-Based Systems using Petri Nets Lukas Voß, Sven Willrodt, Daniel Moldt, and Michael Haustermann: Between Expressiveness and Verifiability: P/T-nets with Synchronous Channels and Modular Structure  12:30 – 14:00 Lunch (Room: M130/131)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Events</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/social/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/social/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday | Wednesday | Thursday
Tuesday &amp;ndash; Welcome reception The welcome reception will be held in Håkonshallen (The King Håkon&amp;rsquo;s Hall) on Tuesday (21st June) at 20:00, sponsored by the municipality of Bergen. Beverages and finger food will be served.
It is important that attendees arrive on time as the doors will be close at 20:00.
    Wednesday &amp;ndash; Conference dinner The conference dinner will take place at Grand Bergen on Wednesday (22nd June) at 20:00.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsors</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/sponsor/</guid>
      <description>Sponsored by</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Information</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/gettingthere/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/gettingthere/</guid>
      <description>Public transportation The tram (Bybanen) runs from the airport (Bergen Lufthavn Flesland) to the city centre (Byparken) at there is also a stop at the conference venue.
For bus tickets and tram tickets, the Skyss App: https://www.skyss.no/en/tickets-and-prices/buying-tickets/skyss-ticket-app/ is recommended.
Getting to Bergen Bergen can easily be reached through its international airport, which is also served by low-cost airlines.
In addition, Bergen can be reached by train via Oslo. Another alternative is the overnight ferry from Hirtshals/Denmark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorials</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/tutorials/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/tutorials/</guid>
      <description>The FCPP AP framework (Monday, 20 Jun) | Model-based SE for/with PNs (Tue, 21 Jun)
 Spatio-temporal modelling and simulation with the FCPP Aggregate Programming framework  Volker Stolz, Western Norway University of Applied Sciences Ferruccio Damiani, University of Turin Giorgio Audrito, University of Turin  Date: Monday, 20 June 2022
Time: 14:00&amp;ndash;17:30
Room: M005
As the density of computing devices in human environments continues to increase, the costs and challenges of maintaining distributed systems rise, driving a search for solutions increasing the autonomy of computing systems while reducing their overall complexity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/workshops/</guid>
      <description>Affiliated workshops Monday  Petri Nets and Software Engineering (PNSE&#39;22)  PNSE Programme   12th edition of the Model Checking Contest (MCC&#39;22)  MCC programme     Tuesday  Algorithms and Theories for the Analysis of Event Data (ATAED&#39;22)  Programme   International Health Data Workshop (HEDA&#39;22)  Programme    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Papers</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/cfp/</guid>
      <description>Call for Tool Demonstrations (Read more &amp;hellip;)
Call for Papers - Affiliated Workshops (deadline passed)  Petri Nets and Software Engineering (PNSE&#39;22): https://www2.informatik.uni-hamburg.de/TGI/events/pnse/ Algorithms and Theories for the Analysis of Event Data (ATAED&#39;22): https://www.fernuni-hagen.de/ataed/ataed2022/ International Health Data Workshop (HEDA&#39;22): https://cs.ttu.ee/events/heda-2022/  Call for Papers - Main conference (deadline passed) The 43rd International Conference on Application and Theory of Petri Nets and Concurrency will take place in Bergen, Norway on 19 June - 24 June, 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Tool Demonstrations</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/cftd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/cftd/</guid>
      <description>Call Tool Demonstrations - Session of Petri Nets 2022
The Petri Nets conferences are the premier venue for researchers active in the field of analysis, design and specification of concurrent systems.
Alongside the main conferences and their call for papers, an informal tool demonstration session is organized. Note that, this is a separate event from the dedicated tool-paper-track of PN 2022. The tool demonstration session is intended for researchers and practitioners, to show their recently developed tools to the other conference attendants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proceedings</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/proceedings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/proceedings/</guid>
      <description>The proceedings of the main conference is published by Springer-Verlag as volume 13288 in the Lecture Notes in Computer Science Series (LNCS).
Participants registered for the conference have free online access to the proceedings of the conference.
LNCS Proceedings of Petri Nets 2022
The organisers have received 50 physical copies of the proceeedings. As there are more than 50 participants registered for the main conference, we have prioritized to provide authors of papers accepted for the main conference with a physical copy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tool Demonstrations</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/tools/</guid>
      <description>Alongside the main conferences there will be a tool exhibition and demonstration from Wednesday until Friday in the same room as the coffee breaks. The tool exhibition will be opened as part of the tools session of the main conference on wednesday afternoon combined with a light serving of finger-food and drinks.
The following tools will be part of the tool exhibition
 ecco I ❤ Petri Nets ePNK Tina GreatSPN Titan IOPT-Tools   ecco Franck Pommereau, IBISC, Univ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/registration/</guid>
      <description>Registration form and payment Registration for the conference (including Petri net course, workshops and tutorials) and payment is done via the link below
IMPORTANT NOTE Registration may be temporarily closed due to maintenance of the Proviso-system. In that case try again later - or contact the organising chairs.
Registration
Registration fees (late registration) Deadline for early registration was is June 1.
For very late conference registrations participation in the conference dinner cannot be guaranteed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>General inquiries about Petri Nets 2022 can be addressed to the organising chairs
 Lars Michael Kristensen (Western Norway University of Applied Sciences) Violet Ka I Pun (Western Norway University of Applied Sciences)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Committees</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/committees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/committees/</guid>
      <description>Organisation chairs
Lars Michael Kristensen (Western Norway University of Applied Sciences)
Violet Ka I Pun (Western Norway University of Applied Sciences)
Workshop chairs
Gianfranco Ciardo (Iowa State University)
Robin Bergenthum (Fern Universität in Hagen)
Petri Nets course and tutorial chairs
Jorg Desel (Fern Universitet Hagen)
Jetty Kleijn (Leiden University)
Program committee chairs
Laure Petrucci (University Sorbonne Paris Nord &amp;amp; CNRS)
Luca Bernardinello (University de Milano Bicocca)
ACSD track chairs
Jörg Desel (Fern Universität in Hagen)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Important Dates</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/dates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/dates/</guid>
      <description>Submission deadline for the main conference has passed.
Submission to affiliated workshops is still possible
 Petri Nets and Software Engineering (PNSE&#39;22): https://www2.informatik.uni-hamburg.de/TGI/events/pnse/ Algorithms and Theories for the Analysis of Event Data (ATAED&#39;22): https://www.fernuni-hagen.de/ataed/ataed2022/ International Health Data Workshop (HEDA&#39;22): https://cs.ttu.ee/events/heda-2022/  Overall schedule for the conference
         Petri Nets course  19 June - 20 June 2022   Workshops 20 June - 21 June 2022   Tutorials 20 June - 21 June 2022   Main Conference 22 June - 24 June 2022    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/overview/</guid>
      <description>Programme Overview | Session Schedule
.tg {border-collapse:collapse;border-spacing:0;} .tg td{font-family:Arial, sans-serif;font-size:18px;padding:10px 10px;border-style:solid;border-width:0px;overflow:hidden;word-break:normal;} .tg th{font-family:Arial, sans-serif;font-size:18px;font-weight:normal;padding:10px 10px;border-style:solid;border-width:0px;overflow:hidden;word-break:normal;} .tg .tg-1wig{font-weight:bold;text-align:left;vertical-align:top} .tg .tg-lyu2{font-weight:bold;background-color:#0085a1;color:#ffffff;border-color:#0085a1;text-align:center;vertical-align:top} .tg .tg-fymr{font-weight:bold;border-color:#0085a1;text-align:left;vertical-align:top} .tg .tg-0pky{text-align:center;vertical-align:top} .tg .tg-0lax{text-align:left;vertical-align:top} .tg .tg-separate{border-width:2px;border-style: double none none none;border-color:#0085a1;} .tg .tg-sesstech{font-size:16px;text-align:center;vertical-align:top;border-width:1px;border-style:none double none none;border-color:#0085a1;} .tg .tg-sessbreak{font-size:16px;text-align:center;vertical-align:top;background-color:#C0DFE7;border-width:1px;border-style:none double none none;border-color:#0085a1;}  Programme Overview  Sunday
19 Jun Monday
20 Jun Tuesday
21 Jun Wednesday
22 Jun Thursday
23 Jun Friday
24 Jun   PN Course
Time:9:00-17:00
Room: M125 PN Course</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
