<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PETRI NETS 2022</title>
    <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on PETRI NETS 2022</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Petri Nets 2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://petrinets2022.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/home/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Petri Nets 2022 The 43rd International Conference on Application and Theory of Petri Nets and Concurrency and affiliated workshops, advanced tutorials, and Petri netts PhD course will take place in Bergen, Norway on 19 June - 24 June, 2022.
Submission of papers to one of the affiliated workshops
 Petri Nets and Software Engineering (PNSE&#39;22): https://www2.informatik.uni-hamburg.de/TGI/events/pnse/ Algorithms and Theories for the Analysis of Event Data (ATAED&#39;22): https://www.fernuni-hagen.de/ataed/ataed2022/ International Health Data Workshop (HEDA&#39;22): https://cs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accepted Papers</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/accepted/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/accepted/</guid>
      <description> To be announced
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programme</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/programme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/programme/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Established in 2004 by the International Institute for Software Technology of the United Nations University (UNU-IIST, currently known as the United Nations University Institute in Macau), the ICTAC conference series aims at bringing together researchers and practitioners from academia, industry and government to present research and exchange ideas and experience addressing challenges in both theoretical aspects of computing and the exploitation of theory through methods and tools for system development. ICTAC also aims to promote research cooperation between developing and industrial countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RV Lectures @ ICTAC</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/rvlec/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/rvlec/</guid>
      <description>RV Lectures @ ICTAC, Nov. 30 / Dec. 1 Supported by the Norwegian Research Council FORSTERK-project COEMS Training Network.
Volker Stolz, Jose Ignacio Requeno, Martin Leucker Runtime Verification of Streams with TeSSLa Sandro Stucki, Gerardo Schneider, Cesar Sanchez Gray-box Monitorability of Hyperproperties &amp;ndash; the Case of Data Minimization Ezio Bartocci et al. Monitoring Cyber-Physical Systems Dejan Ničković Runtime verification for rigorous engineering of cyber-physical systems Giles Reger Monitoring with Data  Practicalities  Venue: Online (Zoom) Time: tbd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Bergen</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/bergen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/bergen/</guid>
      <description>The city of Bergen Bergen is a world heritage city and the gateway to the Fjords of Norway. The city is well-connected to all major European flight hubs.
  More information on VisitBergen
Bergen Weather Heard bad things about Bergen weather? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, we&amp;rsquo;ve ordered reasonable weather! Check the forecast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accommodation</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/accommodation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/accommodation/</guid>
      <description>Bergen is full of centrally located hotels, which are 5-6 tram stops (around 10 mins) away from the conference venue (tram stop: Kronstad). Here we list some hotels in various price ranges in decreasing order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carl Adam Petri Speaker</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/paulo-verissimo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/paulo-verissimo/</guid>
      <description>Prof. Paulo Esteves-Verissimo (King Abdullah University of Science and Technology, Saudi Arabia)  Assumptions in computer science: mere mathematical hypotheses, or representations of the physical world? [Abstract in PDF]
The praxis of algorithm or mechanism design, especially in concurrent or distributed systems, mandates clear statements of the assumptions underlying the design, such as topology, dimension, synchrony, performance, threats, etc. The design &amp;mdash; say, of an algorithm whose behaviour is defined by a set of properties (safety, liveness) &amp;mdash; is then shown correct by demonstrating it does secure those properties, given the assumptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference Venue</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/venue/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/venue/</guid>
      <description>The conference will take place in the K2 building at Campus Bergen of Western Norway University of Applied Science. You can easily reach the building from either Bergen city centre or Bergen airport by tram (disembark at Kronstad stop).
  
Western Norway University of Applied Sciences Western Norway University of Applied Sciences is one of the largest higher education institution in Norway with approximately 1,800 employees and 16,000 students distributed on five campuses in Førde, Sogndal, Bergen, Stord and Haugesund.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invited Speaker</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/diekert/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/diekert/</guid>
      <description>Prof. Volker Diekert (University of Stuttgart, Germany)  Petri Nets and Mazurkiewicz Traces Partnership when Honeymoon is Forgotten [Abstract in PDF]
History. In the mid 1970-ties it became clear that free partially commutative monoids play a central role for the analysis and the understanding of concurrent systems. The foundations were developed in the 1973 JACM-paper by Robert Keller [1]. A few years later, in 1977 Antoni Mazurkiewicz published his seminal Aarhus technical report where he showed that, indeed, partial commutation describes the semantics of one-safe Petri nets perfectly [2].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invited Speaker</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/huisman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/huisman/</guid>
      <description>Prof. Marieke Huisman (University of Twente, the Netherlands)  VerCors and Alpinist: correctness of GPU applications throughout the development cycle GPU programs are widely used in industry. They make use of special hardware, supporting massive parallelism. To avoid the introduction of errors, we can augment GPU programs with (pre- and postcondition-style) annotations to capture functional properties. The VerCors program verifier, a verifier for concurrent software, has been tailored to reason about such GPU programs, and in this talk I will explain how this is done, and discuss various GPU case studies that have been verified with VerCors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keynote Speakers</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/keynotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/keynotes/</guid>
      <description>Carl Adam Petri Speaker  Prof. Paulo Esteves-Verissimo (King Abdullah University of Science and Technology, Saudi Arabia) Assumptions in computer science: mere mathematical hypotheses, or representations of the physical world? (Read more &amp;hellip;)

 Invited Speakers  Prof. Volker Diekert (University of Stuttgart, Germany) Petri Nets and Mazurkiewicz Traces Partnership when Honeymoon is Forgotten (Read more &amp;hellip;)

 Prof. Marieke Huisman (University of Twente, the Netherlands) VerCors and Alpinist: correctness of GPU applications throughout the development cycle (Read more &amp;hellip;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local Weather</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/weather/</guid>
      <description> Updated weather forecast will be provided later.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Main Track</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/mainconference/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/mainconference/</guid>
      <description>The main conference takes place from Wednesday to Friday, 22 - 24 June 2022. The three days before the main conference also offer a wide range of activities.
It is also possible to arrange meetings and courses related to Petri Nets and concurrency. Submissions for such activities must contain a 2-5 page description. They must be received by the Workshops chairs via email no later than January 13, 2022.
List of accepted papers for the main conference</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petri Nets Course</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/pncourse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/pncourse/</guid>
      <description>The Petri Net Course takes place from Sunday 19 to Tuesday 21. It offers a thorough introduction to Petri nets in four half-day modules on Sunday 19 and Monday 20, and a full-day tutorial module on Tuesday 21. For successful participation in the entire course, including preparation and examination, three credit points (ECTS) will be awarded. Each module of the course can also be taken separately, without any credit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Events</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/social/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/social/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday | Wednesday | Thursday
Tuesday &amp;ndash; Welcome reception The welcome reception will be held in Håkonshallen (The King Håkon&amp;rsquo;s Hall) on Tuesday (21st June) at 20:00, sponsored by the municipality of Bergen.
  Wednesday &amp;ndash; Conference reception More details are coming.
 Thursday &amp;ndash; Midsummer celebrations Social event in relation to the midsummer celebrations in Bergen. More details are coming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsors</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/sponsor/</guid>
      <description>Sponsored by</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Information</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/gettingthere/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/gettingthere/</guid>
      <description>Transportation Bergen can easily be reached through its international airport, which is also served by low-cost airlines.
In addition, Bergen can be reached by train via Oslo. Another alternative is the overnight ferry from Hirtshals/Denmark.
Useful links: At Skyss.no you will find routes and timetables for public transport in Bergen and the surrounding area.
From Bergen Airport to Bergen city center:
 The tram (Bybanen) runs from the airport (Bergen Lufthavn Flesland) to the city center (Byparken) and takes around 43 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorials</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/tutorials/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/tutorials/</guid>
      <description>Model-based Software Engineering for/with Petri Nets  E. Kindler, DTU Compute, Technical University of Denmark.  Model-based Software Engineering (MBSE) is a catch-all term for software development technologies in which models are more than just &amp;ldquo;nice sketches&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;drawings&amp;rdquo;. In MBSE, models are mostly used for generating some parts of the code automatically from models or for executing models directly. The OMG&amp;rsquo;s Model Driven Architecture (MDA) is probably one of the most prominent approaches in this direction and Eclipse EMF is a very popular technology supporting MBSE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/workshops/</guid>
      <description> Affiliated workshops
 Petri Nets and Software Engineering (PNSE&#39;22): https://www2.informatik.uni-hamburg.de/TGI/events/pnse/ Algorithms and Theories for the Analysis of Event Data (ATAED&#39;22): https://www.fernuni-hagen.de/ataed/ataed2022/ International Health Data Workshop (HEDA&#39;22): https://cs.ttu.ee/events/heda-2022/   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Papers</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/cfp/</guid>
      <description>Call for Papers - Affiliated Workshops  Petri Nets and Software Engineering (PNSE&#39;22): https://www2.informatik.uni-hamburg.de/TGI/events/pnse/ Algorithms and Theories for the Analysis of Event Data (ATAED&#39;22): https://www.fernuni-hagen.de/ataed/ataed2022/ International Health Data Workshop (HEDA&#39;22): https://cs.ttu.ee/events/heda-2022/  Call for Papers - Main conference (deadline passed) The 43rd International Conference on Application and Theory of Petri Nets and Concurrency will take place in Bergen, Norway on 19 June - 24 June, 2022. The conference is organised by the Software Engineering Research Group at Western Norway University of Applied Sciences and will be held at Campus Bergen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/registration/</guid>
      <description>Registration for the conference (including Petri net course, workshops and tutorials) will be available from mid-April.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>General inquiries about Petri Nets 2022 can be addressed to: petrinets2022@gmail.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Committees</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/committees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/committees/</guid>
      <description>Organisation chairs
Lars Michael Kristensen (Western Norway University of Applied Sciences)
Violet Ka I Pun (Western Norway University of Applied Sciences)
Workshop chairs
Gianfranco Ciardo (Iowa State University)
Robin Bergenthum (Fern Universität in Hagen)
Petri Nets course and tutorial chairs
Jorg Desel (Fern Universitet Hagen)
Jetty Kleijn (Leiden University)
Program committee chairs
Laure Petrucci (University Sorbonne Paris Nord &amp;amp; CNRS)
Luca Bernardinello (University de Milano Bicocca)
ACSD track chairs
Jörg Desel (Fern Universität in Hagen)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Important Dates</title>
      <link>https://petrinets2022.github.io/dates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petrinets2022.github.io/dates/</guid>
      <description>Submission deadline for the main conference has passed.
Submission to affiliated workshops is still possible
 Petri Nets and Software Engineering (PNSE&#39;22): https://www2.informatik.uni-hamburg.de/TGI/events/pnse/ Algorithms and Theories for the Analysis of Event Data (ATAED&#39;22): https://www.fernuni-hagen.de/ataed/ataed2022/ International Health Data Workshop (HEDA&#39;22): https://cs.ttu.ee/events/heda-2022/  Overall schedule for the conference
         Petri Nets course  19 June - 20 June 2022   Workshops 20 June - 21 June 2022   Tutorials 20 June - 21 June 2022   Main Conference 22 June - 24 June 2022    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
